[
    {
        "question": "Wen gibt es im ZKRD nur einmal?",
        "answers": ["Markus", "Joannis", "Volker", "Annette"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wer mit öffentlichen Verkehrsmitteln ins ZKRD reist, trifft vermutlich auf welchen deutschen Rekord?",
        "answers": ["höchstgelegene Straßenbahnhaltestelle", "schmutzigster Bus", "längster U-Bahn-Zug", "ältester Bahnhof"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [1, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wenn eine Sache besonders interessant oder gut gelungen war, dann wurde es bis Ende 2020 auch gerne wie bezeichnet? Als…",
        "answers": ["fesch", "attraktiv", "sexy", "reizend"],
        "correct": 2,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "Welche Buchstabenkombination ist für Multiallelcodes nicht gültig?",
        "answers": ["ULM", "CHM", "ZKRD", "JMY"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [1, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "In welchem Jahr wurden die DNA-Klasse-1-Felder im ZKRD eingeführt?",
        "answers": ["1997", "1998", "1999", "2000"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [1, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "In welchem Jahr wurde EDS abgeschaltet?",
        "answers": ["2001", "2002", "2003", "2004"],
        "correct": 2,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Wann gibt es im ZKRD-Geburtagskalender drei Geburtstage hintereinander?",
        "answers": ["13. - 15.10.", "16. - 18.10.", "19. - 21.10.", "22.10. - 24.10."],
        "correct": 2,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "By replacing the last letter of the drink with a specific vowel, which of these alcoholic drinks becomes the surname of a 'Jojo's Bizarre Adventure' character?",
        "answers": ["Brandy", "Sake", "Tequila", "Vodka"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "How many live action versions of 'Assassination Classroom' are there?",
        "answers": ["1", "2", "3", "4"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "Originally, the game 'Donkey Kong' featuring Mario was supposed to contain characters from what other cartoon series?",
        "answers": ["Tom and Jerry", "Popeye", "Flash Gordon", "Beetle Bailey"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "On the anime series 'Cardcaptor Sakura', which of the following is not the name of a card that Sakura Kinomoto captures?",
        "answers": ["Shot", "Steal", "Snow", "Sweet"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Zatch Bell's evil twin brother?",
        "answers": ["Dubois", "Zeno", "Xue", "Robert"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [0, 2]
    },
    {
        "question": "Until 1917, what city was the capital of the Russian Empire?",
        "answers": ["Novogrod", "St. Petersburg", "Vladivostok", "Smolensk"],
        "correct": 1,
        "fifty": [2, 3]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the fate of Generals Montcalm and Wolfe, who led the French and British forces at the Battle of the Plains of Abraham in 1759?",
        "answers": ["Only Montcalm died", "Only Wolfe died", "Both generals survived", "Both generals died"],
        "correct": 3,
        "fifty": [0, 1]
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the first name of Roman Catholic pope Pius XII, who reigned from March 1939 to October 1958?",
        "answers": ["Eugenio", "Giovanni", "Giuseppe", "Angelo"],
        "correct": 0,
        "fifty": [1, 2]
    }
]